(this["webpackJsonphorror-movie-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonphorror-movie-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,r){},15:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(0),i=r.n(s),o=r(8),c=r.n(o),n=(r(13),r(6)),a=r(17),h=r(18),l=r(19),x=r(20),u=[{question:"Which actor made his film debut in A Nightmare on Elm Street?",answers:[{text:"David Arquette",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Ryan Reynolds",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Johnny Depp",isCorrect:!0},{text:"Jared Leto",isCorrect:!1}]},{question:"Which actor played the killer in Se7en?",answers:[{text:"Brad Pitt",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Morgan Freeman",isCorrect:!1},{text:"John Cusack",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Kevin Spacey",isCorrect:!1}]},{question:"Who was the murderer in the 1980 slasher Friday the 13th?",answers:[{text:"Pamela Voorhees",isCorrect:!0},{text:"Michael Myers",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Jason Voorhees",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Freddy Krueger",isCorrect:!1}]},{question:"Michael Myer's mask in 1978 movie Halloween is based on which actor's face?",answers:[{text:"James Dean",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Burt Reynolds",isCorrect:!1},{text:"William Shatner",isCorrect:!0},{text:"Richard Dreyfuss",isCorrect:!1}]},{question:'Which horror movie had the tagline "Man is the warmest place to hide"?',answers:[{text:"Alien",isCorrect:!1},{text:"The Thing",isCorrect:!0},{text:"Re-Animator",isCorrect:!1},{text:"The Fly",isCorrect:!1}]},{question:"Which horror movie did the monster/villain attack high school kids through their dreams?",answers:[{text:"The Texas Chainsaw Massacre",isCorrect:!1},{text:"The Exorcist",isCorrect:!1},{text:"A Nightmare on Elm Street",isCorrect:!0},{text:"The Shining",isCorrect:!1}]},{question:"What classic horror movie was originally titled The Babysitter Murders?",answers:[{text:"Halloween",isCorrect:!0},{text:"Scream",isCorrect:!1},{text:"A Nightmare on Elm Street",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Friday the 13th",isCorrect:!1}]},{question:"How many killers are revealed at the end of the movie Scream?",answers:[{text:"1",isCorrect:!1},{text:"2",isCorrect:!0},{text:"3",isCorrect:!1},{text:"4",isCorrect:!1}]},{question:"In the movie Scream what is Rule #1 on Randy's list of rules for surviving a horror movie?",answers:[{text:"Say I'll be right back",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Don't drink or do drugs",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Don't have sex",isCorrect:!0}]},{question:"Which of the following movies was not based on a Stephen King book?",answers:[{text:"Misery",isCorrect:!1},{text:"The Exorcist",isCorrect:!0},{text:"Cujo",isCorrect:!1},{text:"Children of the Corn",isCorrect:!1}]}],d=r(1),m=function(){var e=Object(s.useState)([]),t=Object(n.a)(e,2),r=t[0],i=t[1],o=Object(s.useState)(0),c=Object(n.a)(o,2),m=c[0],j=c[1],C=Object(s.useState)(!1),b=Object(n.a)(C,2),O=b[0],g=b[1],v=Object(s.useState)(0),w=Object(n.a)(v,2),f=w[0],y=w[1];Object(s.useEffect)((function(){q()}),[]);var q=function(){S(),i(u.slice(0,5))},S=function(){for(var e=u.length-1;e>0;e--){var t=Math.floor(Math.random()*(e+1)),r=[u[t],u[e]];u[e]=r[0],u[t]=r[1]}};return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:r.length>0&&Object(d.jsx)(a.a,{className:"quiz",children:Object(d.jsx)(h.a,{children:Object(d.jsxs)(l.a,{sm:12,md:8,className:"mx-auto",children:[Object(d.jsxs)("h1",{className:"title",children:[Object(d.jsx)("span",{children:"Horror"})," Movie Quiz"]}),O?Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("h5",{className:"mt-4",children:"You answered"}),Object(d.jsxs)("h1",{className:"question-count",children:[f," / ",r.length]}),Object(d.jsx)("h5",{children:"questions correct"}),Object(d.jsx)(x.a,{variant:"success",className:"mt-4",size:"lg",onClick:function(){q(),j(0),y(0),g(!1)},children:"Play Again"})]}):Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section mt-4 mb-5",children:[Object(d.jsx)("h5",{className:"question-count",children:"".concat(m+1," / ").concat(r.length)}),Object(d.jsx)("h4",{children:r[m].question})]}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:r[m].answers.map((function(e){return Object(d.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return function(e){e&&y(f+1);var t=m+1;t<r.length?j(t):g(!0)}(e.isCorrect)},children:e.text})}))})]})]})})})})};c.a.render(Object(d.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(d.jsx)(m,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[15,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.bea35220.chunk.js.map